You've implemented the main activity wireframe. So, now, we can move
on to the detail activity wireframe. This is what it looks
like. We have the date, the high and low temperatures, and
then additional weather information. We also have the weather icon and
the weather forecast. And these line up horizontally. Build up the
layout XML for this wireframe. Then modify the detail fragments that
you can populate all this information, including these new views. While
you're doing that, you might as well move the detail fragment
into its own file, so it's separate from the detail activity. At
this point the detail fragment class is getting pretty long so you can
move that into it its own file. Before you get started, I want
to point out that this layout has information taking up a lot of
vertical space. If you rotate your device into landscape mode, or you have
a smaller height device, some of the content could get cut off. So
think about how you can make this layout be vertically scrollable. To show
you what I mean, I added a couple more lines of text at
the bottom of the layout. Then I made the content vertically scrollable
so you can see all the information. So go ahead and make that
change to your layout as well. When you're done with all these
steps, this is what the app should look like. We don't care about
the visual details now. We just want to make sure the functionality is
hooked up, so all the right information is displayed on screen. You can
use the code snippets provided below
for helper functions and strings that you're
going to need. And again, leaving a placeholder image is fine for now